Hi!
In this video clip, I will be showing you step 1 for installing a wide angle door viewer.
This is the door viewer that we will be installing.
It is also known as a peep hole.
In this entry way, there are no windows or other way to tell who is on the other side of that door.
By installing this door viewer, it will really aid in our safety.
You want to make sure when installing your door viewer that you pick a location that looks good on the door.
Obviously the center would look a lot better than if it were on one of the sides.
The next thing to consider is that your height that you are installing your door viewer is that all people living in your household can look through it.
I am going to be installing mine on my center panel and I am going to install it a little under 5 feet up on the door.
This should be a good height for everyone that lives in the household.